Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Fagg, Marcus C.; Beane, Arthur; Kiernan, Frank; Baden-Powell, Robert, Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Levin, Leonard S.; Hocking, Agnes Boyle O'Reilly; Kiernan, Frank; West, James E.; Palmer, Albert W., Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Junior State of Georgia; George Junior Republic of Western Pennsylvania.
  - Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Moffett, Harry C.; Smith, Perry; Baden-Powell, Robert, Feb. 1902 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Proposed George Junior Republic in Florida.
  - Redick, Laura D.; Levin, Leonard S.; Beane, Arthur; Gute, William A., Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    William R. George grant of land to R.M. Schell.
  - Dapping, William O.; Large, Harold; Tuck, Charles H.; Fagg, Marcus C.; Crane, Robert, Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Excerpts of William R. George and Esther George correspondence. (Annotations.)
  - George, Orra Kelsey; Large, Harold; Hurley, John W., Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Murphy, Starr J.; Franklin, Ruford; Gute, William A.; Miller, Susan Dixwell, Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    George Junior Republic of New Jersey; Proposed Republic in Washington State.
  - Levin, Leonard S.; Crane, Robert; Barran, Rose C.; Stafford, Hartwell; Freeman, Mary A., Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Account of William R. George's trip through Montana and Washington State; George Junior Republic of Western Pennsylvania.
  - Margesson, David; Moffett, Harry C.; Smith, Bolton; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Montague, George, Feb. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    A New Opinion on the Junior Republic" by Robert Baden-Powell; Excerpts from diary of William R. George. (Annotations.)
  - Baden-Powell, Robert; Palmer, Albert W., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Program of events for William R. George in California.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Palmer, Albert W., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Crane, Robert; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Smith, Bolton, Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Palmer, Albert W.; Redick, Laura D., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Proposed Junior Republic in Arkansas; Itinerary of William R. George in California.
  - Smith, Bolton; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Stafford, Hartwell; Stoddart, Evelyn L., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Perottino, Terziana; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Platt, H.L.; Moffett, Harry C.; Sibley, Hiram W., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Palmer, Albert W., Mar. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Proposed Junior Republic in Arkansas.
  - Hurley, John W.; Oppenheimer, William; Day, George Parmly, Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Letters from citizens; George Junior Republic of Connecticut.
  - Waterhouse, G.C.; Hurley, John W.; Barran, Rose C.; Lindsey, Ben B.; Large, Harold, Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Lowrie, Kate L.; Hurley, John W.; Kiernan, Frank; Levin, Leonard S.; Fagg, Marcus C.; Seeley, Paul S., Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Proposed Junior Republic in Oregon.
  - Barran, Rose C.; Hurley, John W.; Gute, William A.; Franklin, Ruford; O'Connor, John Joseph, Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Day, George Parmly; Lewis, John N.; Lee, George L.; Perottino, Terziana, Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Platt, H.L.; Franklin, Ruford, Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Lowrie, Kate L.; Baldwin, Dorothy; Eaton, Ernest T.; Beach, Frederick H.; Fagg, Marcus C., Apr. 1912 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Osborne, Thomas Mott; Barran, Rose C.; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; George, Esther B.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    National Association of Junior Republics; Carter Junior Republic.
  - Mitchell, Guy C.; Krauskopf, Joseph; Hurley, John W.; Seeley, Paul S.; Winship, A.E.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    National Farm School; National Junior Republic.
  - Schell, R. Montgomery; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Ballard, Nellie A.; Franklin, Ruford; Krauskopf, Joseph, May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Levin, Leonard S.; Krauskopf, Joseph; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Forbes, Alexander; Hurley, John W., May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell, Guy C.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Levin, Leonard S.; Lindsey, Ben B., May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    "Report of the Committee on Child Welfare"; Houghton-Mifflin Company, publication of Citizens Made and Remade; "The Spread of the Junior Republic Idea."
  - Krauskopf, Joseph, May1912 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Mitchell, Guy C., May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Lane, Homer T.; Richardson, C. Spencer; Roberts, Margaretta W. (Annotations.), Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lindsey, Ben B.; Barran, Rose C.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Lane, Homer, Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Lane, Homer T.; Clothier, Clarkson, Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newbold, John L.; Bailey, Nettie F.; Mitchell, Guy C., Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    "Some of the Purposes of the National Association of Junior Republics and How It Is Proposed to Achieve Them." (Annotations.)
  - Smith, Bolton; Large, Harold; West, James E., Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Gear, Harry G.; Stoddart, Evelyn L., Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Seeley, Paul S.; Richardson, C. Spencer; Lightner, Clarence A.; Fagg, Marcus C.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Gear, Harry G.; Gute, William A.; Beach, William G., Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Proposed George Junior Republics in Oregon, Florida, and Delaware; Letter from William R. George to Lyman Beecher Stowe.
  - Bailey, Nettie F.; Offer, George E.; McReynolds, Merle. (Annotations.), Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Roberts, Margaretta W.; Fowler, Kate; Crane, Robert; McReynolds, Merle; Franklin, Ruford, Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Fowler, Margaret B.; Smith, Bolton; Smith, J. Reed; Smith, Mamie, Jun. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; O'Connor, John Joseph; Cross, Eliza; Franklin, Ruford; Gear, Harry G.; West, James E., Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Connecticut George Junior Republic; Letters from citizens.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; West, James E.; Baldwin, Dorothy, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    National Association of Junior Republics.
  - Gute, William A.; Beane, Arthur; Dennis, Ralph, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Letters from citizens; Minutes of the Executive Committee of the George Junior Republic.
  - Woods, Philip; Rouse, W.H.D.; Franklin, Ruford; LeRoy, Harris G., Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - List of occupations of former citizens, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hurley, John W.; Preston, H. Clay, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    National Progressive Party; Letters from citizens.
  - Bailey, Nettie F.; Franklin, Ruford, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Franklin, Ruford; Miller, Elizabeth; Bartol, Leah, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    George Junior Republic of N. J.
  - Rouse, W.H.D.; Bills, Elizabeth; Franklin, Ruford, Jul. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Richardson, C. Spencer; Davis, Samuel J., Aug.1912 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Preston, H. Clay; Gibb, Arthur N., Aug. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Preston, H. Clay; Franklin, Ruford; Frost, E. Doreen, Aug. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Preston, H. Clay; Overstreet, H.A.; Richardson, C. Spencer, Aug. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Schmitt, Jacob C.; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; Shanley, Mildred E., Aug. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Levin, Leonard S., Aug. 1912 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Letter from William R. George to Thomas Mott Osborne concerning George's removal from the George Junior Republic. (Annotations.)
  - King, Ruby; Frost, E. Doreen, Aug.1912 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Franklin, Ruford; Overstreet, H.A.; Preston, H. Clay, Aug. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Margesson, Catherine; Roberts, Margaretta W., Aug. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Strawbridge Junior Republic.
  - Fagg, Marcus C.; Franklin, Ruford; Krauskopf, Joseph; May, Paul; Osborne, Thomas Mott; Schell, R. Montgomery; Preston, H. Clay; Smith, J. Reed; Stone, J. Sumner, Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Letters from citizens; George Junior Republic of New Jersey; The New York Times article.
  - Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; Winship, A.E., Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    The New York Times article.
  - Fowler, Kate; Crane, Robert; Frost, E. Doreen; Mitchell, Guy C.; Lowrie, Kate L., Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Treman, Robert H.; Large, Harold; Preston, H. Clay, Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Mitchell, Guy C.; O'Connor, John Joseph; Derrick, Calvin, Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    National Junior Republic; Letter from Derrick to The New York Times.
  - White, Andrew Dickson, Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Booklet of resolutions and signatures of support from the citizens of Ithaca for William R. George.
  - Osborne, Thomas Mott; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Huntting, Benjamin F. (Mrs.)., Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    The New York Times article; Letter from Stowe to the Manager of the Associated Press.
  - Leach, Abbey, Sept. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell, Guy C.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Gute, William A., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Letter from William R. George to Mitchell regarding a citizen's suicide; George Junior Republic of New Jersey.
  - Waterhouse, G.C.; Peck, Grace B.; George, Eleanor B., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Preston, H. Clay, Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Richardson, C. Spencer; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Hocking, Agnes Boyle O'Reilly; Winship, A.E.; Smith, Jacob C., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Letter from William R. George to Stowe.
  - Preston, H. Clay; Wesson, Cynthia M.; Levin, Leonard S.; Bruner, Earle W.; Large, Harold; Peck, Allen D., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    "Some of the Purposes of the National Association of Junior Republics and How it is Proposed to Achieve Them" by Levin and Bruner; Description of the methods of the California George Junior Republic.
  - Myers, Elmer H., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Letter by William R. George to Mrs. Benjamin F. Huntting concerning the petition of support by Ithacans. (Annotations.)
  - Bush, D.V., Oct. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Proposed George Junior Republic in South Dakota.
  - Gute, William A.; McFarland, Jane E.; Bush, D.V. (Annotations.), Nov. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Levin, Leonard S.; London, Jack; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Korff, Alletta, Nov. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Forbes, Alexander; McCormick-Goodheart, Leander, Nov. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Bush, D.V.; Frost, E. Doreen; Levin, Leonard S.; Browning, J. Hull; Smith, Bolton, Nov. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Pathe Weekly Pictures.
  - George, John F.; Barran, Rose C.; Gute, William A., Dec. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Kiernan, Frank; Schmitt, Jacob C., Dec. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Sumner, George S.; Kiernan, Frank, Dec. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Roosevelt, Theodore; Frost, E. Doreen; Smith, Bolton; Peck, Allen D. (Annotations.), Nov. - Dec.1912 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Schell, R. Montgomery (Mrs.); Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; Miner, Stella A.; Rutherford, Minnie U., Dec. 1912 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - "A Plan of Cooperation Between the National Association of Junior Republics and the Freeville Republic.", 1912 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Letter to George Junior Republic Executive Committee regarding rental of William R. George's property; Extracts of correspondence between William R. George and Esther B. George; "A Junior Republic in a City" by William R. George; Descriptive overview of George Junior Republic, its administration and policies. (Annotations.), 1912 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Smith, H.A.; Davis, Samuel J.; Hurley, John W.; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    "Suggestions Regarding a Training School for Republic Workers and Pioneer Citizens"; "Visit of General Baden-Powell to the George Junior Republic"; "Publishing House Scheme." (Annotations.)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Wood, Philip E.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; LeRoy, Harris G.; Oliver, Adele E. (Annotations.), 1912 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "Publishing House Scheme"; Itinerary for California trip; Computations for appraisal of properties, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; Smith, Bolton; Miller, Susan Dixwell; Large, Harold, Jan. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gill, Wilson L.; Smith, Bolton; Bruner, Earle W., Jan. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Gurley, R.H.; Baldwin, Dorothy, Jan. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Proposed George Junior Republic in Virginia.
  - Korff, Alletta; Mitchell, Guy C., Jan. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Winship, A.E. Proposed George Junior Republic in Texas; George Junior Republic of Western Pennsylvania; National Junior Republic. (Annotations.)
  - (Box 14)
  - Perry, Edward W.; Schwab, Erma B.; Wilson, Bird M., Feb. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Proposed George Junior Republic in Nevada. (Annotation)
  - (Box 14)
  - Frost, E. Doreen; McKiernan, William J., Feb. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Letters from citizens; Minutes of the Executive Committee.
  - Brooks, Pauline B.; Bienstock, Nathan S., Jan. - Feb.1913 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Petition to United States Navy.
  - London, Jack; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T.; Fowler, Kate; Baldwin, Dorothy, Feb. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Schell, R. Montgomery; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; O'Connor, John Joseph; MacDonald, Clifford, Mar. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Affidavit by William R. George concerning respondents' freedom to speak re charges against him.
  - Thurston, Henry W.; Large, Harold; Roberts, Margaretta W.; McKiernan, William J.; Gute, William A., Mar. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    The Little Commonwealth; "Superintendent's Report to the Executive Committee"; Strawbridge Junior Republic; Minutes of Executive Committee; Letters from citizens. (Annotations.)
  - Solomons, Aline E., Mar. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Account of the founding and organization of the George Junior Republic; The Young Womens' Fortnightly Club.
  - McKiernan, William J.; Ganyard, Mervin B., Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Kiernan, Frank; Solomons, Aline E.; Wilson, Margaret W., Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Gute, William A., Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Minutes of Executive Committee.
  - Wilson, Margaret W., Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    List of citizens and amounts paid.
  - Solomons, Aline E., Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Solomons, Aline E.; Frost, E. Doreen, Apr. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee; Letters from citizens; Letter from William R. George to Mellnor M. Hersh, May 1913 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Howells, Mary G., May 1913 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Letters from citizens; Letter from William R. George to Lu Stearns. (Annotations.)
  - Mitchell, Guy C., May 1913 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Letters to citizens.
  - Letters to citizens, May 1913 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Gute, William A.; Perry, Edward W.; Offer, George E., Jun. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Winship, A.E.; Large, Harold; Doyle, Clyde; Sumner, George S.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Jun. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    California George Junior Republic; "The Junior Municipality."
  - Gute, William A.; Doyle, Clyde, Jun. 1913 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    "The Junior Municipality"; "A Petition for Independence."
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Mitchell, Guy C., Jul. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    "A Petition for Independence."
  - Lincoln, Allen B.; Mitchell, Guy C.; Gute, William A.; LeRoy, Harris G., Jul. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    George Junior Republic Pledge.
  - Mitchell, Guy C.; Doyle, Clyde, Jul. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Mann, Albert R., Jun. - Jul.1913 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Bolton; Hunter, Mary E., Jul. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Untitled "Story" by William R. George.
  - Hurley, John W.; Doyle, Clyde; Dawson, Charles B.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Aug. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Dawson, Charles B.; Perkins, Katrine C.; Smith, Bolton; Large, Harold, Aug. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    "American Citizens in the Making" by Lyman Beecher Stowe; The Little Commonwealth.
  - Hunter, Mary E., Aug. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    List of citizens arrived and left.
  - Martin, E.R.; Dawson, Charles B.; Levin, Leonard S., Sept. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Letters from citizens; Copy of article in Ithaca Journal concerning Junior Municipality, Sept. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Hunter, Mary E., Sept. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dawson, Charles B., Sept. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Doyle, Clyde; Dawson, Charles B., Oct. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "The Junior Republic Movement" by Lyman Beecher Stowe, Oct. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Hervey E.; Bailey, George, Oct. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Doyle, Clyde; Stowe, Lyman Beecher. California George Junior Republic, Oct. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Peck, Allen D., Oct. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Perry, Edward W.; Stoddart, Evelyn L., Nov. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Sample ballots, Junior Municipality. (Annotations.)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Albertson, Henry H.; Judd, Zechia; McReynolds, Merle, Nov. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    National Republic; Junior Municipality of Cortland.
  - Mitchell, Bernice; Beach, William G.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Nov. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Meacham, Standish; George, Mary B., Nov. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Letter from C. Spencer Richardson to Lyman Beecher Stowe; "A Junior Republic in a City" by William R. George. (Annotations.)
  - Campbell, Augusta E.; Card, Glenn F.; George, Orra Kelsey; Perry, Edward W.; Fowler, Kate; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Philadelphia Republic. (Annotations.)
  - Buckner, Emory R.; Choate, Joseph H.; Hunter, Charles F.; Perry, Edward W., Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Investigation of William R. George; New York State Board of Charities. (Annotations.)
  - Offer, George E.; Frost, E. Doreen; George, Orra Kelsey; Dwight, John W., Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Burden, Henry, Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    New York State Board of Charities. (Annotations.)
  - Franklin, Ruford; Huntting, Benjamin F. (Mrs.)., Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Petition of support from citizens to William R. George; Letter from William R. George to citizens of the Junior Municipality. (Annotation)
  - (Box 15)
  - Ganyard, Mervin B.; Heberling, James S.; Hurley, John W., Dec. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Petition of support from citizens of the Junior Municipality of Ithaca, N.Y. (Annotation)
  - (Box 15)
  - Searles, Frank, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    A Petition for Independence from the youths of Ithaca, N.Y.
  - Abbott, Lyman; Gaither, Nina Williams, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Letter from ex-citizens expressing support for William R. George; Untitled article by William R. George; "A Junior Republic in a City"; Description of the George Junior Republic; National Junior Republic. (Annotations.)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    National Junior Republic; Proposed George Junior Republic in Ohio; Statement by William R. George concerning financial affairs at the George Junior Republic; Untitled articles about problems, events, and life at the George Junior Republic.
  - "Publishing House Scheme"; "Self Government" by William R. George. (Annotations.), 1913 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Stoddart, Bessie D.; McReynolds, Merle; Childs, Billy, Jan. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Letters from citizens. (Annotation)
  - (Box 15)
  - White, Andrew Dickson, Jan. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Peck, Allen D.; Albertson, Amy, Feb. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Wilson, Bert, Feb1914 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Hotchkiss, Willard E., Mar. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Gill, Wilson L.; Albertson, Henry H.; Peck, Allen D.; Bruner, Earle W., Mar. 1914 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - McKiernan, William J.; Lindsey, Ben B., Apr. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Coombs, Morton B.; Isham, Ethel H.; Margesson, Catherine, Apr. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell, Guy C., May. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Heberling, James S.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Day, George Parmly; Sumner, George S., May. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Connecticut George Junior Republic.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Day, George Parmly; Kiernan, Frank; Bernstein, Ludwig B.; Doyle, Clyde, Jun. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    List of Self Government organizations.
  - Gute, William A.; Childs, Billy; Richardson, C. Spencer; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Jun. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    National Association of Junior Republics; Children's Village, Meadowbrook Pennsylvania.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T., Jun. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Junior Municipality of Cortland, N.Y.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; LeRoy, Harris G.; Smith, Jacob G.; Childs, Billy; Brister, C.W., Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Junior Municipality of Auburn, N.Y.; Press release concerning the Self Government Training Camp. (Annotations.)
  - Stowe, Hilda Beecher; Brooks, Pauline B.; LeRoy, Harris G.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Brooks, Walter D., Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Searles, Frank; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Preston, David S., Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    "Junior Citizens in Action" by Lyman Beecher Stowe; Letter to William R. Hereford describing the eight Junior Republics.
  - Condolences, Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; LeRoy, Harris G., Jul. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Condolences. (Annotations.)
  - Howland, Isabel; Hotchkiss, Willard E., Aug. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Angier, Roswell P., Aug. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hurley, John W.; Burr, George Lincoln; Forbes, Alexander; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Smith, Jacob G., Sept. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Statement of William R. Hereford.
  - Beach, William G.; O'Connor, Timothy J.; Rosenthal, Herman, Sept. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    "A Junior Republic in a City"; Letter from William R. George to Esther George concerning actions of the Board of Trustees, George Junior Republic.
  - Schell, R. Montgomery; Stowe, Lyman Beecher. (Annotations.), Oct. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Richardson, C. Spencer; Levin, Leonard S.; Heizer, Charles W., Oct. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    "Reopening" of George Junior Republic. (Annotations)
  - Baldwin, Dorothy; Hurley, John W.; Albertson, Amy; Bills, Elizabeth, Oct. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Winship, A.E.; George, Esther B.; Osborne, Thomas Mott; Forbes, Alexander; Thurston, Henry W.; Richardson, C. Spencer; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T. (Annotations.), Nov. - Dec.1914 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Brewster, Esther A.; George, Esther B.; Offer, George E.; Albertson, Henry H., Jan. - Sep.1914 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Obituary; Draft of untitled article about the George Junior Republic and the founding of a George Junior Republic in Ithaca, N.Y. (Annotations.)
  - Heizer, Charles W.; Baker, A. Alvord; George, Esther B.; Beach, William G. (Annotations.), Oct. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Sherman, Eileen, Nov1914 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Winship, A.E.; Omessa, Henri, Dec. 1914 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the National Association of Junior Republics; "Social Law Story"; "The Junior Republic." (Annotations.), 1914 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Hurley, John W., 1914 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Proposed George Junior Republic in North Carolina; Farm census forms.
  - Schell, R. Montgomery; LeRoy, Betty, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Form letter of acceptance to George Junior Republic; Statement of conditions; "School Children as Census Takers"; "The Junior Republic" annotated.
  - "The Junior Citizen" by Edward Spengeman; "Memorandum on the Application of the Junior Republic Idea to Other Institutions" and "Remaking Men in the Philippines" by Lyman Beecher Stowe, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Omessa, Henri; Rosenthal, Herman; Thacher, Sherman Day; Hotchkiss, Willard E., Jan. 1915 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Omessa, Henri, Feb. - Mar.1915 (Box 17, Folder 2)